Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim. (In the name of Allah, the compassionate, the merciful)
Now that they have captured Osman...
they want information.
They think that they'll have the treasure.
Sir...
What's your command?
You'll go to the castle as the ambassador.
Tell them...
Edebalı will give you the treasure.
But...
if they let Osman out.
Sir...
We have struggled for years to have them.
Lots of our friends died.
Is it worth for Osman?
We took back the dignity of the World of
Islam from them, Akçaderviş.
But Osman is as valuable as the treasure.
But will we really give
them the treasure, sir?
If we take Osman, then yes.
I'll be waiting for Yannis.
Let us go with you, father.
Go to Kayı Tent, Bala.
If anything crucial happens
there, let us know.
The devil is also there.
Take care of it if necessary.
Your command, father. Where are you going?
Ashes to ashes, dust to dust.
May our holy war be blessed.
Hit me! So...
life will squirt instead of blood!
Hope will squirt!
Hit me!
Hit!
Talk! Where is Edebalı?
Talk! Or I'll kill you...
and your men. (Alps)
Talk!
Where?!
Come closer...
Come closer.
He's in our hearts.
In my heart.
In all of Turk's hearts including me.
If you are strong enough...
take him!
Devil! Come!
- Boğaç.
- Come!
No.
- Boğaç!
- Brother.
Boğaç!
Brother!
My Bey...
Boğaç...
I hear a weak groaning, Osman.
- Do you hear it too?
- Lions roar, Sofia.
They don't groan.
Our dungeons are full of bones
of lions, Osman.
Hold on, brother. Hold on.
Allah is eternal!
Boğaç!
Allah says in Al-Baqarah...
"Or do you think that you
will enter Heaven...
while such [trial] has not yet come
to you as came to those...
who passed on before you?" [2:214]
Allahu Akbar! (Allah is the greatest.)
- Allahu Akbar! (Allah is the greatest.)
- Shut up!
- Shut these dogs up!
- Allahu Akbar! (Allah is the greatest.)
Allahu Akbar! (Allah is the greatest.)
Here! It's the picture of my victory!
Dündar Bey, I know who has done it.
Tell us what to do.
Kayı's horses will make Kulucahisar Castle
unbearable to unbelievers.
What does it have to do with Kulucahisar?
Sofia and Kalanoz came to our tent.
They want friendship.
We don't know who has done this.
Süleyman Shah's tent!
What is that? Your tent...
don't know the difference
between friend and foe!
I saw that devil's treachery!
How can you not see her real face?
This tent isn't like where you come from,
Selcan Hatun.
This tent is sensitive...
and it has deep politics.
If you hadn't run away
from your husband...
you would've known it.
Your mind is poor, your mouth is pedant.
You try to teach us politics without
looking at yourself.
Your time is up, Selcan Hatun.
If you try to barge in, I won't be just
pedant, you should know.
Look at this panache, Bamsı.
She thinks that she's a Sultan.
Don't make me angry.
- Pull yourself together, Zöhre!
- Shut up!
Selcan Hatun.
Selcan Hatun...
If you dare to talk that way
again in front of me...
I'll cut your tongues.
Now, leave the field of
contest to us, men.
Mind your own businesses. Hatuns!
Out!
- Dündar Bey...
- I said out!
Dündar Bey...
It's obvious that Kayı's
torment is forgotten.
Bring them into line as soon as possible.
Osman is my son.
We can't sleep or rest...
till we find him.
But something big is going on.
To rescue Osman...
we'll lie in ambush like a
wolf, roar like a lion...
and we'll be cunning.
Now, listen to me carefully.
Big devil...
Welcome.
You'll all die.
Our biggest pleasure is to
persecute you, Osman.
Pain is fine.
Suffering is fine.
Don't get nervous, Osman. We have time.
We'll listen to your sayings, Osman.
Princess Sofia. Well done.
Turks will do some things.
They'll look for Osman in the castle.
They shall keep
thinking that you're an angel.
Don't worry, sir.
Good luck, Osman.
Gündüz Bey...
We can't underestimate things that are
said.
Go to the castle with
Bamsı Bey and meet Sofia.
Make them feel my anger.
Tell them...
If our friends involve in preparing
Osman's trap...
we'll kill them one by one.
Your command, my Bey.
Thanks, Dündar Bey.
I have some business with that centipede.
You're going there for Osman, Bamsı Bey.
Don't forget it.
And we won't have unfinished businesses.
Batur...
You must send your Alps (men)
to everywhere.
Your eyes are strong, your
ears are strong.
They'll search everywhere.
If they find a trace...
let us know.
Your command.
I thought you were cleverer.
You fell prey to me in
your first struggle.
It's too early to celebrate your victory.
We just began.
Thank Allah that...
I have an enemy like you.
Did you learn these
words from your father?
You want to know where
Sheikh Edebalı is, right?
You want to find where the treasures are.
Actually, I don't care about your
treasures.
I just want to destroy your dignity.
If you take possession of
a nation's belongings...
you take their honor.
I already have so many of these treasures.
You may take our treasure...
but...
not our soul.
Happiness goes, traditions
stay, says our ancestors.
We rivet our traditions to our
hearts and minds.
Even if there's only one
Turk left in the world...
it means that our traditions are alive!
And that one Turk's aim...
to wreck your rule!
Here, Osman Bey.
You must be thirsty.
You're so angry, Osman!
Is it ready?
Ah, fire!
Fire that melts the mountains!
Show us your strength!
- Degenerated!
- Devil!
You have nice friends, Osman!
When you're hurt, they yell!
Is that all you can, Yannis?
Witness my victory, Osman.
Megela.
Where is Edebalı?
Where is Edebalı?!
In the name of Allah, the
compassionate, the merciful.
"Indeed, We have given you, (Muhammad),
a clear conquest...
"That Allah may forgive for you what preceded of your sin and what will follow and...
complete His favor upon you...
...and
guide you to a straight path."
"And Allah may aid you
with a mighty victory."
"It is He who sent down tranquillity into
the hearts of the believers...
...that they would increase in faith along
with their [present] faith."
"And to Allah belong the soldiers of the heavens and the earth...
...and ever is Allah Knowing...
... and Wise." Surah Al-Fath [48]
Allah.
Allahu Akbar! (Allah is the greatest.)
Enough!
Enough.
I'll tell where Edebalı is.
I'm listening, Osman.
Where is Edebalı?
Master Yannis! Master Yannis!
- Allah is eternal!
- You dogs!
Sir...
Master Yannis! Master Yannis!
Any news from Osman Bey, Batur?
Aren't you his servant? You
couldn't save your Bey.
We've brought enemies to their knees...
but we also have enemies inside.
Inshaallah, you don't betray us.
Or I'll kill you.
You couldn't save your Bey but
you keep showing off here.
If you were that brave...
what were you doing when
Osman was abducted?
You're evil, Batur.
But I promised Bamsı Bey.
I won't be like devil till we
make the enemies kneel down.
If I hear
one more treachery...
no one can save you from me!
That's enough, Samsa.
Go to Kayı Tent and obey my father
Dündar Bey now.
Our Ertuğrul Bey gave the
power to my father.
My Allah, you're the greatest.
What is this visit for?
That's not a visit, Sofia.
We're here to call out.
An attack, maybe a betrayal.
You'll tell us which.
I don't know what you're talking about.
What attack? What betrayal?
Osman Bey and his Alps (men)
have been attacked.
No need to talk more.
If this has anything to do
with Kulucahisar...
you should be frightened.
You're threatening us in our lands,
in our castle, Gündüz Bey.
We don't, Kalanoz!
It's a command of Dündar Bey, son
of Süleyman Shah.
If you are the people who
killed our Alps and...
intended to kill our Beys ...
Kayı's wrath will be on you.
I swear to Allah...
we'll come to your door with our horses.
We'll break your door with punches...
and we'll make your
tombstones with it.
I swear to Allah, we will Sofia.
We will.
I know you're in pain, Bamsı Bey.
We're your most powerful ally.
Why do we do something like this?
We killed traitor Yannis.
Just to strengthen our friendship.
I lost my husband for this deal.
If anyone prevents this deal to happen...
I'll kill him!
Commander Kalanoz!
It's my order to all soldiers
in Kulucahisar Castle.
Osman Bey, our powerful ally who
is the Bey of Kayı Tent...
will be searched everywhere.
Everything that hurt
him will be destroyed.
Until we hear from him, we won't stop.
Your command.
Stop feeling suspicious
about us, Gündüz Bey.
As long as there is peace, we'll all win.
Thanks.
Princess Sofia, thanks.
Sofia...
These eyes, these eyes...
saw so many cunnings looking like a sheep.
At the end, these cunnings' peltries
became my shoes.
You should know that.
Come on, my Gündüz.
Let's go.
Thanks, Bamsı Bey.
Sir, are you okay?
He's powerful.
Like a tiger.
He won't talk.
When he's sober, continue torturing him.
- Where are you going, sir?
- To the castle.
Edebalı will reach me for Osman.
Your men should be careful.
Your command, sir.
Kayıs smell the blood quickly.
He is Marcus!
Yes, it's him!
Why are you here, traitor? Traitor!
What are you doing here?
Priest Marcus!
Traitor! What are you doing here?
Kill him! Kill him!
Tursun!
Soldiers! Take him!
If anyone interferes, he'll be dead.
You'll take me to Sofia.
Edebalı sends his regards.
Eat it. Eat.
Easy, easy!
Don't die. I need you.
Why are you doing this?
What do you want from me?
Even if we're on different sides...
we have the same enemy.
Osman.
Listen to me carefully.
Osman is trouble when
both alive and dead.
Tell me where he is.
I have to protect the
dignity of my father.
I don't care about your father's dignity.
I can't tell you where he is.
I want him...
dead...
not alive.
Osman is an obstacle.
We go hunting, he is the head hunter.
We organize something, he
is the head of it.
Osman is always the most powerful!
And I'm always the one who is in the back.
If I don't kill him, I'll always
be in the back.
I'll kill you...
or I'll give you double the money
you have in your lap.
There is not much to think of. You want
Osman's head from me.
Just tell me about the gold.
I'd even kill my father.
I'll be waiting at the riverside.
Bring me Osman's head by the night.
But, no gold until I see his head.
Know that.
That was a good agreement.
Is anyone here?
Well, you're here, son.
Edebali!
Who else do you need?
Where are you?
The creatures called humans, keep their
loved ones in their hearts, son.
Don't look for me anywhere else.
Thank heavens! Thank heavens!
Edebali!
They tied my hands and arms. I'm helpless!
I have no more strength.
Find real freedom in serving Allah, and
you shall never be captured, son.
What is all this pain for?
How do I get out of this?
The solution is within the trouble.
You'll see.
Take this, son.
Take it.
Separate the clay from the mud.
Separate it, so that you learn it.
Learn it, so that you get wiser.
The real treasure is knowledge,
little Osman.
Treasures are only apparent to those
who know how to see them.
Did you think Allah who sees, hears,
knows everything...
... has forgotten about you?
Do you think his servant came
and tied you up?
Clear yourself of your doubts, son.
Separate the clay, and reach the treasure.
"For indeed, with hardship [will be] ease."
Surah Ash-Sharh (The Relief) [94:5]
"For indeed, with hardship [will be] ease.
Bala Hatun.
Easy there. Your speed is racing
your shamelessness.
We kick you out from the door,
you enter from the chimney.
Aren't you ashamed?
You don't know morals, just like how
you don't know your place.
Since when it is in the Turkish law
to kick the guests out?
I know what to say, but you don't
know where to stand.
You came here and caused a lot of trouble.
Osman will die because of you!
How much more blood do you want to
be spilled? Isn't it enough?
Do you cry like this in every
slight inconvenience?
As if you grew up in a palace, and
not in the tent.
Aygül sister, if you have big dreams,
keep your heart ready for it.
So it doesn't get crushed during
every struggle.
If you raise those hands to me again,
I'll poke your eyes out.
Hatuns!
Aygül!
What is going on in the middle of
the Tent?
Troubles are raining on us, aunt Selcan!
Because of them!
And now they are back on our door like
they have no shame!
Bala, go to the pavilion.
Mind your own business now. Come on!
Aygül, seems like you're forgetting.
Let me remind you.
You're the daughter of a Bey.
Your biggest ornament is your politeness.
That's the first thing.
Osman risked his life for Bala Hatun.
From now on, no one can separate them,
including you. That's the second thing.
Remember these words.
Don't push my patience too much.
That's the third thing.
What is this, Andreas?
What do you think you're doing
appearing before me with a simple priest?
Relax, Sofia.
Your old friend has come to visit you.
- What's there to get angry about?
- Soldiers!
Take another step and Andreas dies!
I brought Edebali's offer.
Master Yannis was right
again, Priest Marcus.
You came on your own.
You'll bring the treasure too.
I'm listening.
Not a single word until Yannis comes.
I'll wait for him here.
I hope I don't disturb you much.
- Is there anything new from Osman Bey?
- No.
Nothing new. But I know all of this is
that redhead's doings.
Kulucahisar's devils are playing with us.
They don't know what really
matters is destiny.
Only if I could demolish that
castle of theirs!
Let Osman Bey come back first, then it
will be their turn.
Allah knows what will happen to my Osman.
Osman is our Tents prosperity.
May Allah protect him.
My father sent me here after hearing
about Osman Bey.
He wants to give you a helping hand.
May Allah bless you.
Looks like you get along pretty well.
Don't people listen to Beys in
this Tent anymore?
Are unwelcome ones highly respected now?
!ARABIC!
Thank you, my Allah. Thank you.
My Allah! My Allah!
My Bey!
A lion who passes out after being beaten.
You should see it's claws too.
Allah is eternal!
Allah almighty!
Did you lose yourself, now
that your Dündar Bey is a deputy?
If my Bey is a deputy, then I'm
Kayı Tent's Hatun.
If someone does wrong, I'll level them.
No one else is needed.
Good. You'll start with your
daughter then.
Tent's Hatun...
Dündar Bey neither wants Edebali, nor
his daughter in this Tent.
Whatever the Bey says, nothing more.
That's what our traditions say.
Pity.
Since when did you get old enough to
teach me our traditions, Zöhre?
If you are to teach old Selcan the
traditions...
... may Allah help those traditions.
- We--
- You...
... have confused shamelessness
with decency, my sweet girl.
Now go with your mother, and think about
what you have done.
Think, so that you can understand
how patient Selcan Hatun is.
And about Bala Hatun. She is my guest.
She is always welcome.
If even the Bey himself comes, he can't touch
my guest without stepping on my dead body.
Know that.
Not enough? Tell your Bey the same thing.
As you say, Hatun.
Every man for himself.
Expect yourself to be responsible for
what will happen to you from now on.
Zöhre!
I have two legs.
Before I stumble on both of you, return
to your Tents.
Don't make me boil! Leave with your
own will and...
... don't make me kick you out.
Come on now!
What was that?
Come on.
What's going on in there?
Priest Marcus!
How nice seeing you here once again!
As long as you stay in these lands,
you'll see us every day.
Where is the treasure?
The thing that you call treasure, is
in one's heart, Yannis.
No surprise that you look
for it so desperately.
Does Edebali want Osman, or not?
My master told me that he'll
give you what you want.
Where is Edebali?
He's waiting for you near Akçadede.
But, if he doesn't see Osman
Bey alive and well...
He will not be bringing the treasure.
Megala!
Take Osman to the place he's
talking about.
I will be waiting for you there.
If this is a trap, both Osman
and Edebali will die.
Faster you idiots!
You're finally mine, Osman Bey.
You tricked us! You dog!
I'll kill you just like that Kanturalı
you have sent to kill me.
Kanturalı!
Dogs like you cannot bite Kanturalı!
Dündar Bey's foolish son Batur...
He wants your head.
Batur?
Not only you, your dogs around
you also fear me to death.
I see it in their eyes.
Your death will be fun.
Allah almighty!
I'm here cousin!
Die!
Batur!
Konur Alp!
Show no mercy! Hit them hard! No mercy!
Bamsı Bey! Sergeant Samsa!
- Allah is eternal!
Brother!
Batur! What should I say, you came
right on time.
- Thank you.
- How did you find this place?
Juan fell into my trap.
He brought me to you, brother.
Bless you.
Bless you too.
Thank you Batur Bey.
You played those devil's sons good.
Brother!
Thank Allah!
Samsa!
Bamsı Bey!
Boğaç!
He's not doing good.
- Osman!
- Abdurrahman Gazi!
Thank Allah!
So that means my father is back!
Brother! My father...
Abdurrahman Gazi, where is my father?
Please tell me! Where is my father?
Our father is sick, brother.
From now on, our Bey is uncle Dündar.
How the years pass by!
The shining face of my Hayma ana, the rich
sound of my Süleyman Şah!
My little Osman's naughty behaviors.
Sit here, I'll show you something.
These are Osman's. Look!
His sweater.
- So small!
- Right? So small.
He was a lion back then, he's a lion now.
I knitted that lions first mane.
He grew up, bloomed, used swords
with Bamsı Bey, Turgut Bey.
Allah made him a valiant, his father
Ertuğrul Bey made him a master swordsman.
He would always shine among
all the children in the Tent!
His arrow was the first to hit, he was
the first to leave the wooden sword!
His peers always followed him.
He grew up and became a Bey.
His friends became Alps.
Thankfully they never got separated.
Selcan Hatun. There is
something I'm wondering.
Ask me, my girl.
Come on ask me, don't be shy.
Osman Bey...
Has he fallen in love before?
I wouldn't know that, my girl.
But I know how the light in his
eyes shine when I say Bala.
I'm Osman's mother. I know him well.
If I was a mother for him, you
should know this.
Bala Hatun is written in Osman's heart.
I know it from how his voice thrills, how
his eyes shine when I say Bala Hatun.
Just like yours.
It seems to me that my Allah has tied
your hearts together.
- I hope for the best about you.
- Allah willing.
Allah willing!
Osman Bey is coming!
Thank Allah!
Thank heavens!
www.Kurulusosman.online
My Allah brought you back to us, Osman.
Thank you, uncle.
You made me very proud.
You saved Osman with the help of Allah.
Thank you, my son, thank you.
Long live Batur Alp!
May Allah bless you, cousin.
You too, cousin.
Thank you, Dündar Bey, for these problems
that have been burning our hearts are solved.
But we wonder, how could
Batur Alp handle this?
By using his head, Selcan
Hatun, by using his head.
I have the key to save Osman, father.
Also, if we save him, your Beyhood
in the Tent will be reinforced.
- How?
- I have that man called Juan.
He will take us to Osman.
Attack there with Bamsı Bey then.
Zöhre.
I can take care of my Osman.
Aunt.
May those who did this to you be
drowned in their own blood, son.
Osman, when you feel better...
... come to the tent.
Will do, uncle.
Will do.
Osman.
- Bala Hatun is in the Tent.
- Is she, aunt?
- Go.
- Thank you.
Prisoners escaped.
Master Yannis.
We are leaving!
I got out of hell...
... and came to you.
My Allah granted me
the heaven, Bala Hatun.
I begged for every second.
Thank Allah, you are here, safe and sound.
Allah made me the
happiest person, Osman Bey.
But you are exhausted.
May the hands of those who did these to
you be broken, may their bloodline perish!
- You should be in the healing tent.
- Don't you know...
... that your words are
medicine for my wounds.
Your eyes are the light that
shine through my nights.
I have forgotten my pains now.
You should forget them too.
"Indeed, Allah is with the patient."
Surah Al-Baqarah [2:153]
Where is this Edebali?
Or is this a game too?
I assure you, that my
master sees you, Yannis.
Edebali.
Soldiers!
All those years have worn you, Edebali.
From the young boy that
I saw in the Âhi Evran...
... to this old man.
It depends on how you look at it, Yannis.
I am young enough to
fight you at all times...
... and old enough
to die at any time.
It seems these nonsenses
didn't help you.
Here you are.
And you know you will die if
you don't give me what I want.
Those who die for their cause live longer
than their executioners, Yannis.
You are not going to give up, are you?
That fighter spirit in you makes
you stubborn like a goat.
You can't even see the
defeat coming at your door.
Allah ordered us to
fight with the tyrants.
Allah is the one who
gives victory or defeat.
We will accept whatever
outcome Allah shows us.
Pity, such a pity that you still believe
you can change the system I built.
Not just the system, we will
change the era, Yannis.
This reign of tyranny you have
built will be destroyed.
The great...
... Osman...
... the grandchild of Süleyman Shah.
Look at your wounds very carefully.
Look at your wounds...
... so that you can see your tomorrow.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
[In the name of God, the merciful and compassionate.]
Let your wounds burn you, Osman Bey.
Let them burn...
... so your flame keeps getting stronger.
Let them hurt you, Osman Bey.
Let them hurt...
... so you know where you stand.
Things that are done to you...
... are the signs of what
you will do to them.
Don't you forget that.
You haven't changed at all.
Now that we are waiting for
the treasure and Osman...
... I would want to hear how you trained
these men that are loyal to you to death.
Our hearts are in the
hands of Allah, Yannis.
It is impossible to see this
light, understand this...
... loyalty from the well of
infidelity that you fell in.
I infiltrated right next to you.
I've trained hundreds of men
that are loyal to us in the soul.
The sense of unity of
the Muslims are over, Edebali.
You can believe you'll
resurrect that soul.
I will gather new souls with the
gold that I will take from you.
I will hit you with the ones
who were with you.
There are such brave ones between us...
... that their souls
are priceless, Yannis.
Neither ranks, gold, nor
any other mortal things.
They feed with Dhikr, wear gratitude,
and fight with patience.
But you aren't even aware of this,
because you are a pawn of your devil.
Don't forget that the devil's
former name was Azazel.
Guardian of Heaven, and teacher of angels.
You share the same fate.
Your passion for victory, and
pride is making you a devil.
If it's the victory in the
end, I don't care at all!
But I wonder, why is Osman
so important to you?
Are you planning to give the wooden
sword of Ahmet Yesevî's to him?
Fate is making its nets, Yannis.
Brave people like Osman
will end people like you.
Osman.
My Batur, my valiant son...
May Allah help you and make
your sword sharp at all times.
Amin, mother, thank you.
Everything has changed in the Tent.
May Allah grant all
fathers a son like you.
I would die in your path, father.
Edebali sent his daughter to the Tent.
You should get Edebali away
from Osman, Dündar Bey.
Or we will have more
trouble in the future.
Is the girl in Osman's tent now?
Yes, father.
I fear that she wants to marry
Osman and settle in the Tent.
That would be the end of Kayı Tent.
Come on, come with me!
Let's see what they are up to.
- Thank you, Aybüke.
- Enjoy.
Thank you.
Thank Allah, our Tent
is peaceful again.
Thank Allah.
Now, If I make my Osman marry
too, I can die in peace.
What is it, Dündar Bey?
I've heard that Bala Hatun is here.
I want to talk with her about that.
Why did she come to the Tent?
Are those things that happened
have a connection with Edebali?
Tell me, girl, how could
your father contact Alps?
He saw them in his dream.
So, he saw them in his dream.
If he only could see them earlier,
Osman wouldn't be attacked.
Allah is the one who saves and destroys.
Bala Hatun says what she knows.
What, you also don't
believe in dreams now?
You can talk about this with my father.
Thank Allah for giving
Osman back to you.
Thank Allah.
Thank Allah he's returned.
But how could we know whether this fight
tries to kill him, or someone we know...
... again?
We were living in peace
and unity in this Tent.
All these troubles emerged
with the arrival of Edebali.
- Uncle.
- I am talking Osman, I am!
Bey of the Tent!
Now...
... hear what I will say.
I don't want unity in
this Tent to be deformed.
I don't want people
causing trouble in my Tent.
We did not see...
... scattering and being
ruined from our ancestors.
We saw helping each other, and being one.
Leave us alone from now on, Bala Hatun.
That is enough, we do not want
any more trouble and curse.
Now to you, Osman. If you continue to...
... work with that Edebali, know that
you will not get our help anymore.
I understand, Dündar Bey.
May Allah keep you away from
any kind of trouble and curse.
If you'll excuse me.
Come on, Gonca Hatun.
Osman.
You endured many troubles.
But now is the time to
make up your own mind.
Edebali, his daughter, and his dervishes
brought nothing but trouble into this Tent.
Bala Hatun has no place in this Tent.
Uncle!
What are you saying?
Sofia held the dagger that
opened my wounds.
Trouble is coming from the infidels!
Neither Sheikh Edebali nor his
daughter had anything to do with it.
On the contrary.
We highly value them.
Osman.
You are at the crossroads now, Osman.
This Tent is the place you belong to.
Know who you rebel for.
I...
... wouldn't just rebel for her.
I would be a sword and
strike if necessary!
And you...
... should know it like this.
Bala Hatun!
Calm down.
Even if the whole world
try to take you from me...
... I would bow before no one!
I know, Osman, but no one should
be in trouble because of us.
No one should be without their homes,
Ahîs can't stay out of trouble.
I would die for the trouble
that's coming from you, Bala Hatun.
Tell me, where is Edebali?
I will send my Selcan aunt
and ask to marry you.
He went to the Ahîs.
He went to the Ahîs?
Then what are you doing here?
My father thought that
would be best, Osman Bey.
Bala Hatun.
Tell me, what are you hiding from me?
I can't tell you this, Osman Bey!
Bala Hatun.
Why can't you tell me, Bala Hatun?
I can't, you are the future of this Tent.
I wouldn't want you to be in more trouble.
My father wouldn't want that either.
Now, let me go.
Come on!
Bala!
Now you are telling me
where your father is!
What is going on?
If you don't tell me the truth,
you can't get out of this Tent.
My father...
... he sent me here after he
heard what happened to you.
I understood that he is going
to sacrifice himself for you.
Then...
... Yannis has him.
He is going to give Yannis
the treasure for you, Osman Bey.
How could he do this?
Do you know where he went?
Believe me, he didn't say
to me either, Osman Bey.
I still remember his words before leaving.
He said, " We came from the soil,
we will return to the soil."
Remove the clay, give it to the treasure.
Sheikh Edebali.
I know.
I know where he is.
Stop worrying, Bala Hatun,
I know where your father is.
How?
First, I will save Sheikh Edebali
from those infidels...
... then I will ask him to
let me marry you.
After we get over this too, we
will be happy if Allah permits.
You have ruined everything.
You can't even be
satisfied with your victory.
As long as this woman is with
you, your Tent won't be peaceful.
What is it, Selcan Hatun?
Are you trying to end my marriage?
No, I am trying to save the Kayı Tent.
Aunt Selcan.
You came here as a guest. We are honored.
But don't try to meddle with
the business of this Tent.
Or I will have to end your visit here.
When you are a Bey, you will
rule over someone eventually.
But don't you forget.
You are not a Bey.
You are just a deputy.
They've escaped.
Where is Osman, Megala?
They've escaped, sir.
They also killed all of our men.
Attack! Kill them all!
Osman!
I am here, my Sheikh!
Master Yannis!
Master, they outnumbered
us, we have to go now!
You go, I will distract them.
No.
You should turn it a little bit more.
Look at my Bala.
How excited she is!
It's good now.
You're pretty, Masha Allah (praise be).
We have gone through a lot of troubles.
We have risen from the dead.
However...
I have never been more excited, Gonca.
My Lord has gifted you with love,
that's why, Bala Hatun.
- May it continue like this, in sha Allah.
- In sha Allah (if Allah permits).
Selcan Hatun will be here soon.
My Allah, may you gift me with calmness.
You are a rose that has not been
bloomed yet in your father's garden, Bala.
You are his precious one.
I don't know if my sheik gives you to
Osman Bey.
My father abandoned the treasure for
He has risked his own life.
His feelings about Osman is clear.
This marriage will satisfy him too.
You are right. My sheik keeps
talking about Osman Bey's braveness.
He trusts him.
He wouldn't entrust you to anyone but him.
Then, tell me.
What do you want first?
A girl or a boy?
I just want a propitious child.
May our Lord give us the best.
- In sha Allah.
You have fought for us
and face death.
Live long, Osman Bey.
I girt on.
But, I heard that...
you risked your life for me, Edebalı.
They tortured you.
How did you manage to save yourself?
I got out of that dark well thanks to
your light, Edebalı.
It's not about looking, it's about
seeing, son.
As you can see it, that light
is inside you.
In sha Allah, that light will brighten
Oghuz's horizon.
Then, what about the darkness in my heart,
Edebalı?
Why did you refuse me when I came
to you?
That you refused me hurt me a lot.
Excuse my naiveness.
Forgive me, Edebalı.
My Sheik, Edebalı.
I am not the one to forgive.
But, I know that the one who knows his
mistakes is on the right path, son.
Your path is good, so is your intention.
Just preserve yourself, and protect your
heart.
Father.
Who did this to you?
Osman!
Call a doctor. Now!
Megela...
Megela is dead, my daughter.
Don't panic, sir.
We will take revenge.
What happened?
Where is Edebalı?
Where is Osman?
Everything is obvious now.
My daughter, from now on,
it's just about blood!
Sir Yannis.
Juan died because of his foolishness.
What about you, Salvador?
What are you going to do about your
clumsiness?
It was an unlucky situation of Juan,
Kalanoz.
In fact, in Kulucahisar Castle, clumsy
ones are more precious.
- What do you mean, Salvador?
- It's clear.
While I was out there fighting with
my men, you...
Enough!
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
[in the name of Allah, the merciful and compassionate.]
I have freshened up.
- You made this.
- Yes, father. May it heal you.
It tastes like your deceased Mother's
Rose Sherbet (beverage).
May my Lord gift her grave with glory,
in sha Allah.
In sha Allah.
What a wonderful daughter you left for me
Ulduz Hatun.
May Allah gift you with his merciness.
How are you, father?
A lot happened, I couldn't ask you.
Osman Bey is free.
The treasure is safe now, thank Allah.
Thank Allah.
But, there are so many troubles waiting
for Osman.
- May my Lord help him.
- Amin.
Father.
I want to tell you something,
but I feel shy.
Don't be shy, my beautiful daughter.
Tell me.
Osman Bey.
Osman Bey told me...
Tell me, daughter.
What did Osman Bey tell you?
He will send Selcan Hatun.
To ask for me in marriage.
Say, "He will give them life who produced
them the first time;
...and He is, of all creation, Knowing."
[It is] He who made for you from the green
tree, fire, and then from it you ignite.
Is not He who created the heavens and the
earth Able to create the likes of them?
Yes, [it is so]; and He is the Knowing Creator.
His command is only when He intends a
thing that He says to it, "Be," and it is.
So exalted is He in whose hand is the realm
of all things, and to Him you will be returned.
[Yasin Surah 19-23]
"Glory to thy Lord the Lord, of Honour and Power! (He is free) from what they ascribe (to Him)! And Peace on the Messengers!
And praise to Allah, the Lord and Cherisher of the Worlds." (Surah as-Saaffat, 180-182)
Reciting Surah Al-Fatiha (The Opening) [1]
My martyred...
brother.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
[in the name of Allah, the merciful and compassionate.]
Demirbüken.
Brothers...
We will take your revenge.
We will.
They will be drowned in the blood they
shed, brother.
We will take revenge.
We will.
To make this land our home...
so many valiants have died.
So many fathers buried their sons
with their own hands.
Their lovers have been abandoned.
No!
This is not just a war!
These lives will not be wasted!
This fight is the fight between
good and evil!
We are not going to stop until we
demolish the evil!
We won't, my Osman!
- Of course we won't!
- We will not give up!
We will stand!
We put on our weapons until the true
religion of Allah dominates!
This fight is the fight between
cross and crescent!
- Allah-u Akbar! (Allah is the greatest)
Welcome, Selcan Hatun.
Thank you. I want to see Sheik Edebalı.
I have something to tell him.
Our master is praying for our martyrs
right now. Can you wait?
Finally your face smiles, Osman Bey.
What makes you so?
Tell me so that I can smile too.
I am waiting for my Aunt Selcan, Aygül.
She went to ask for Bala Hatun
in marriage.
Really?
May Allah make you happy.
- May it go well.
- Amin.
Bala Hatun and his father don't cause
trouble, in sha Allah.
But, you know that since they have come to
our tent, we have had a lot of troubles.
Don't talk like that, Aygül.
Trouble comes from Kulucahisar.
May Allah keep Edebalı among us.
As to Bala...
Don't speak of her like this.
I don't want to hurt your feelings.
Okay, Osman Bey.
Okay.
Won't you wish happiness for me?
I'll marry Alişar Bey soon.
Aygül...
You are our pearl in this tribe.
I see you as a sister.
May Allah give you the happiest home.
May you be always happy.
Welcome, Selcan Hatun.
Thank you, my beautiful daughter.
I am happy to see you.
- Thank Allah, we are fine now.
- Thank Allah.
We will see better days, in sha Allah.
I am here to see Sheikh Edebalı for a
good purpose.
Here, Selcan Hatun.
Congratulations, Bala.
May you marry soon.
Allah gives the best.
Aygül.
What happened?
Nothing, mother.
Then why are you crying?
Tell me.
Mother, I know, you're going to go mad.
But I can't stop it, tolerate me.
Osman.
What did he do?
Why did he make you sad?
He didn't do anything to me, mother.
Selcan Hatun.
Selcan Hatun has gone to see Edebalı.
What is she doing there by herself?
Also, what does she have to talk to with
Edebalı?
Bala Hatun.
She will ask for Bala Hatun in marriage
to Osman.
Look at that.
Is it her place to act while Osman's
uncle is here?
They lost it.
Dash away your tear.
It is because of your vain hopes
about him.
Your future is bright, my daughter.
You are going to be a wife of a banner
lord and a Hatun of your tent.
If Osman goes like this, he will do
nothing but causing trouble.
Be grateful instead of crying like
a child.
We have got over a challenging situation,
Selcan Hatun.
Thank Allah.
May my Lord make us happy from now on.
Amin.
The one to thank is Allah, of course.
However, you did a lot, too.
You protected my Osman.
May Allah bless you.
A valiant never walks alone, Selcan Hatun.
Even if there is no one with him,
if he is with Allah, he is not alone.
We did nothing.
Everything happens thanks to our Lord.
My son Osman challenged with his faith
and got out alive thanks to his faith.
Sir, you are calling Osman "son".
We want to call Bala Hatun "daughter".
Bala Hatun is a very well educated girl.
If you allow, we want her to brighten our
tribe up.
With Allah's order and
our Prophet's word...
We ask for your daughter Bala's hand for
our son Osman.
Thank you, Hatun.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
[in the name of Allah, the merciful and compassionate.]
I want to tell you something, father.
Do you allow?
Come here, my daughter.
Here, come.
I thought it over, father.
If you allow, I give my consent to
the marriage with Alişar Bey.
Is this what you want, my daughter?
Do I or your mother affect your decision?
No for sure, father.
My tent comes first.
I know that our tent's fate depends on
this marriage.
So...
What about your future?
I just want to see you happy, father.
May Allah give you the best, my daughter.
May this marriage bring happiness to you,
power to our tent, in sha Allah.
In sha Allah.
In our tradition, Hatuns found home,
and husbands protect it.
If you wish a happy marriage, know this...
Flue with smoke, wife with husband.
You ignited me with love.
Now, without you...
there is only death for me, Bala Hatun.
Our Holy Lord ordered marriage for us.
Marriage is sacred.
And marriage is a good purpose, for sure.
Osman Bey is a strong and fearless man.
I know that he is a valiant and a strong
warrior.
As to Bala...
Bala has been educated with Allah's rules.
Of course I want her to marry someday.
However, marriage requires equality.
If there is no equality, there will be
problems.
What I am saying is...
Osman and Bala are not equal.
I don't want to hurt your feelings.
But, I don't consent to this marriage.
My Osman, why are you not eating?
Your meal is still there.
Your heart beats so loud that I can hear
it from here.
Eeh, Bamsı Bey, love issues make you
stop eating.
Once the wedding ceremony is ready,
I will show everyone how to use a sword!
Oi, Oi my sharp weapon Osman.
You are old enough to marry, huh?
Masha Allah (praise be).
Once this marriage happens...
I will slaughter forty rams and give this
tribe a feast of food.
Sergeant Samsa, you should marry too.
He is famous with his weapons,
Konur brother.
Mind your own business, Alps.
Get off my back.
Erkut Alp, you are very quiet.
What is it?
Let him be, Abdurrahman Ghazi.
He just wants all of us to marry...
so that he can eat meat every day.
Aunt.
What happened, aunt?
Why are you upset?
My Osman.
Sheikh Edebalı...
didn't approve.
He didn't give his consent.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com